[Music]
thank you for calling andrus bank
meeting mr chalene help me assist you
today
i actually have a question about my
debit account
sure i can help you with any questions
you have regarding your debit account
great because there's a transaction in
my account that i don't understand
i see well uh thank you for letting us
know about this immediately so i can
check your account transactions
uh may i have your account number please
yeah it's 0.903
thank you please be with me while i pull
up your account information
sure
and uh for verification purposes may i
have your first and last name please
yes it's orlando
a taylor
thank you mr taylor which charge in your
account would you like to check on
uh
hang on let me get my eyeglasses here
okay it's the charge on the third the
amount is three hundred dollars even
yes i do see the charge on the third
uh mr taylor by any chance do you recall
making a purchase from that merchant
no i don't think so i don't believe i
made that purchase
okay well uh if you like i can contact
the merchant for you and ask them about
it
sure that would be great i'd appreciate
my pleasure mr taylor my pity and hold
for a few minutes
sure take your time i'll be fine
thank you
[Music]
thank you for reading mr taylor i was
able to reach the merchant
and
they said that an order was placed and a
delivery was made to your address
that sounds hard
yeah it is
uh by the way mr taylor is there any
chance a family member may have used
your card
well i'm not sure i will have to check
on that
okay so uh mr taylor if that is not the
case please call us back and we will
resolve the issue okay
certainly thanks so much for your help
joining
you're welcome mr taylor is there
anything else that i could further
assist you with
no that's all for now okay thank you for
calling andrew's bank mr taylor have a
good one
bye
you too dear bye
[Music]